Thank you for watching!
Winner gets a lucky clown treat!
I'd love to win that.
I'll do my best
Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
That's good.
Look out!
The result is that the par team wins.
Thank you very much.
So, you two have a lucky biello as a reward.
We just want to eat like we normally do, so we'll follow you.
So let's go Lucky Biello!
Let's go!
Lucky Biello's restaurant
I'm sure you want to win at least once.
My goal should be very ambitious, so my target is very low.
But there might be a miracle win.
This time, I want to learn from the other teams and see how they throw.
I'd like to learn from the teams around me.
Please take a look!
Also, I'd like to thank all the fans who responded to my question on Instagram.
Everyone answered me!
Squid sashimi or soup curry?
You guys are amazing!
They sent me a restaurant.
A hamburger called Lucky Pierrot!
It's close, close, close. I think you can walk there from Hakodate station.
Hokkaido is famous for Lucky Pierrot.
Everyone tells me the name of the restaurant.
Gentle.
Back here.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
I'm on the Shinkansen.
Shinkansen.
Wait a minute.
It's facing this way.
This is a player.
They're lost.
I'll do my best in the tournament.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Good luck, please do your best
I love you
Please share your enthusiasm.
Please be enthusiastic.
Enthusiasm.
Come here, come here, come here.
Yes, I'm enthusiastic.
For now...
I'll do my best in the qualifying round.
Here you go.
It's hot, so don't touch it.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best so that we can go to the hot springs.
I'll have your support.
Yay!
Looks delicious!
I'll leave it to you.
This is my second time eating Genghis Khan.
I love it.
I love it! It's so good!
It's my first Genghis Khan.
Yes, sir!
It's a good sound!
I'm having dinner with everyone for the first time.
Match starts tomorrow!
Let's do our best!
Aim for the championship!
Let's go for it!
Go for it!
The meat is like this!
First of all, Genghis Khan!
The meat is like this...
It's your first time to eat it, isn't it?
Yes, it's my first time too.
Oh, Onta, is it your first time?
Ah...
Can you do it now?
I can do it.
Oh my God, I'm so excited!
I want to try it with vegetables.
I want to try it.
It's hot. Be careful.
I think it's good.
You're a good cook.
It's so beautiful.
So delicious!
Yes, yes...
Umami!
Umami. Umami.
Yum!
Bon appétit! So cute!
How many times have you eaten this?
I eat a lot on tour. Everyone eats when they're exhausted.
I never get to eat at a leisurely pace.
Is it hot? I'm a cat person too. It's fine.
How is it?
It's soft! Soft!
It's really tasty. It's got no smell, and it's really easy to eat.
YEAH!
reference
Boo!
It's good, isn't it?
It's not peculiar at all!
Very good!
Hi Natsumi
Nice to meet you.
How do you like it?
It's not weird at all.
It's very chewy.
I'll give you the full report.
This one came out and it's really good.
It's so good!
Speaking of delicious, slut!
Thank you for watching!
Here we are at the ramen shop!
First time to eat ramen
First time in Hokkaido
Apodate Ramen!
I was looking forward to it.
I wanted to eat a lot of things.
This was one of them.
I'm starving.
Then eat.
What'd you get?
Miso curry ramen.
We're all the same.
It smells so good.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm waiting.
Oh, my God!
The smell alone makes me happy!
I topped it with coconut palm too!
It's so nice!
Looks delicious!
I love beautiful women!
I like beautiful women.
How do you like it?
Put it in the soup.
It goes really well with butter.
It goes surprisingly well with curry.
Good report!
Noodles are good.
Curry
Curry in moderation
Very tasty!
This Hokkaido
Delicious
Wow, buttery rich. Yes, how is it?
Too good!
And one more time.
Oh no!
Noodles are bad!
The soup is something I've never had before, but I've never had it before.
It's a little new.
I see.
Okay, I'll have some.
Thank you very much.
How is it?
Delicious.
I heard later that it's a mixture of curry and miso.
Ne.
Wow, fried rice is here!
Fried rice is here.
Looks delicious!
Oh, man!
It's rich and clammy!
I know what you mean.
Delicious!
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Yum
Too rich.
It's rich, but...
But it's refreshing.
You won't be able to stop eating it.
I'm sure of it.
Miso and curry are good!
Oh, yay!
It's here!
They're here!
It's on the house!
Yay!
So we went as an instrument sharer.
We went with instrument sharers!
There were so many people lined up!
So many people lined up!
The two of us were rewarded
Reward clowns!
What did you order?
Cheeseburger and onion rings with a shake
I'll have fries and orange juice.
We're not having cheeseburgers, are we?
Egg burger.
Cheeseburger!
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious
Look at this
This looks delicious!
Voluminous!
Voluminous and warm!
It's so amazing!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
The cheese is so soft and cheesy!
Yum!
Delicious!
The milk is purifying.
Nice food report!
Can't wait to eat it!
I can't wait to eat it!
I can't wait to try it!
How sweet, the meat is delicious, the cheese is tender, and the filling is too filling!
It's the best tasting!
I can't wait to try it!
I was afraid I wouldn't be able to come because it was so crowded.
But we made it!
Would you like a burger?
I do.
You don't eat.
Well, here you go.
It's called a hamburger. I love hamburgers.
You do?
I'm going into the bookstore.
Oh, seriously, it's super...
It's funny.
It's so good!
A photo I want to take
It's photo time!
It's so good!
Feels like a girlfriend
So cute!
She's so cute.
I want her to be my girlfriend.
This one.
I bought this one.
I bought a soft serve ice cream.
It comes with honey vinegar.
I really wanted to eat vinegar.
I wanted to eat vinegar.
I really wanted to eat vinegar
More than ice cream
I wanted to eat vinegar
I bought it after much hesitation
How is the taste?
Thank you for watching!
The ice cream is good, too.
Good, good, good.
I just had a bite.
It's so good!
Honey and ice cream are both delicious.
It's good.
Yay.
I enjoy sightseeing.
We're going to have fun.
Yay.
Delicious.
Yay!
Cheers!
I have three kinds of beer.
There are three kinds of beer: Bizen, Alt, and Ale.
I'll start with the Beitzen.
I'll have this one, like this.
What does it say?
Ale?
Ale.
I'll start with an ale.
Yay.
Hmm?
Yum! It's so light!
Delicious!
Very fruity! Very light!
Great!
Yay!
How long has it been?
Mork, how long has it been? About a year now, I think.
Oh, it's been?
It's been a year?
There are a lot of stanfalls on various sites.
Various, like the Morita Cup.
I haven't done well yet.
But Natsumi is really good.
Not at all.
She's really good.
We have to be active.
Everyone was pretty good today.
She's getting really good.
So we'll do it once a week or so.
That's right.
You have to practice.
If I practice a lot, I'm sure I'll get good at it.
I'm sure I'll get good at it. That's normal.
Even everyone can exercise.
I'm having fun like this.
I'm having fun.